[EP21]
Last night,
you weren't afraid that she would really choose the first option,
marry into the Ling family,
and do something else against you?
The things she did before
were because she had no choice.
Now that I've given her a choice,
she won't take that old path.
Yes,
people always need to have choices.
But my parents,
they didn't have a choice.
They were
arranged by feudal society.
They hated each other all their lives,
and even
didn't like me very much.
They...
weren't good to you?
I don't have much of an impression
of my mother.
I only remember
when I was a child,
every time I greeted her,
she just walked away.
Mother,
I come to greet you.
Mom, why do you ignore me?
Why don't you like me?
I've done everything
Grandma told me to do.
What about Commander Ling?
My father
always shows tenderness to others,
but only scolds me.
He never asked me
what I really wanted.
You're so young and you don't learn well.
Can you take things from the pond?
Are you listening to me?
You still do such bad things.
What should I do in the future?
How can you inherit the family business?
How can I teach you?
Still not talking?
Second Uncle, Second Uncle.
Look at the windmill.
Okay.
You blow on it.
Let me blow on it.
Xueqiu is really well-behaved.
Grandma.
Grandma told me when I was little
I was born
to repay the Ye Family's debts.
Affection
is the most useless thing in the world.
Ling Shenxing,
do you know?
Your existence
is for the Ye Family.
Why are you looking at me?
Did you hear what I said?
Stand still.
I'll make you remember!
Hands out!
I remember!
Can you stop beating me?
Hands out!
Don't move!
Ling Shenxing,
today, I'll make you remember
your mission
is to lead
the Ling and Ye families forward!
In this world,
no one loves you.
No one loves you.
Do you know that?
Don't cry.
You must be strong.
You must be successful.
Do you know that?
You must support
the Ling and Ye families.
You must understand.
Do you understand?
Don't be sad.
You still have me.
Don't think about
those unhappy things.
Being a parent doesn't require a test.
Not all parents
are born to be parents.
Accepting that they won't love you
is harder
than
loving them.
Do you remember the Qiqiao Festival?
When I went back to find the plaque,
I found
so many plaques with your name on it.
Some are from the people of Yang City,
and some are from the soldiers.
Your parents may not know how to love you,
but the people of Yang City love you.
I love you too.
You have me.
Fortunately,
I have you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Abao should
wake up soon.
What's going on?
The Young Marshal planned to take me away,
but he ran into Young Master Chu.
He was afraid of alarming them,
so he detained me for two more days.
He found a prisoner with a similar figure
to make a substitute.
By the way,
before I fell into the well,
did I say anything unusual?
Or
mention anyone suspicious?
You scolded Old Madam Ling.
Miss Ye.
And you said Second Concubine
cried on a stranger's shoulder,
fearing it would ruin the family's reputation.
What's
her surname?
Shen.
Her family controls
all the water sources in Yang City.
You also mentioned
that the Ling family
rely on Shen Family
for water supply.
Yang City?
Water source?
[News!]
[Yang City is hit by plague.]
[Ling Shao Shuai is unfilial,]
[and deserves divine punishment.]
Get out!
Ling Shenxing, come out!
How can you be so unreasonable?
The plague is rampant.
It's the Ling residence that has been treating you,
and delivering medicine to you.
How can you believe the rumors so easily?
Bah!
The newspaper has written it.
The disaster was brought by you.
Can the Ling residence be irresponsible?
The newspapers in Yang City are all controlled by Chu Nanfeng.
He's trying to bring down Ling Shenxing,
so he spread the rumors.
I have to go find him.
Chu Nanfeng,
did you spread the rumors?
Did you cause the plague?
You're only half right.
You taught me that.
Did you forget?
See that dancing man?
That's my father.
Look at him.
He's so happy.
My stepmother was my mother's maid.
When my mother was pregnant,
she slept with my father.
My mother was so angry
that she died in childbirth.
What a pity.
In this world,
I'm the only one
who remembers my mother.
Your mother
wouldn't want to see you like this.
Easy for you to say.
And his son
shouldn't let the man who killed him
prosper.
How can you repay a kindness
if you repay evil with kindness?
There are only so many resources in this world.
Some gain,
some lose.
I don't want to lose.
If you want something,
you have to fight for it.
I want Yang City,
and you.
I have to do something big.
You're crazy.
As long as you announce in the newspaper
to break off with Ling Shenxing,
and marry me,
I'll immediately announce
the prescription for the plague,
bringing peace to Yang City.
How does that sound?
Isn't this deal
quite favorable?
You really caused the plague?
You're so heartless,
you...
A man who doesn't look out for himself
will be doomed.
I'm just doing my job.
Nonsense!
The saying
means
if people don't cultivate their morality,
they will be punished by heaven.
It's not an excuse
for selfishness and profit!
[I like your fierce]
[and hot temper.]
What should I do?
Do you remember this sachet?
This is
the gift you gave to Commander Ling.
I could catch Ling Shenxing's flaw
thanks to your help.
You are very smart.
You know to replace the things in this sachet.
But unfortunately,
you missed a detail.
The real problem
is this rope.
This rope?
It was soaked in a special solution
for 49 days.
My family
is familiar with it.
As long as you follow this scent,
you'll naturally find
the person you want.
Crazy man!
You've set up such a big trap.
what do you want?
I just want you to hear
the sound
of this gun
shooting Ling Shenxing.
You won't win.
I will die
in front of you
so you can never have me.
What did you put in the incense?
Smart.
I put Tendon-Softening Powder
in the incense.
But don't worry,
it won't kill you.
It just makes you temporarily powerless.
As long as you behave,
I'll make you happy for life.
Help me!
Shenxing!
It's too late.
The moment you walked in,
I had your divorce papers
with Ling Shenxing
published in all the newspapers.
Now everyone in Yang City knows
that
you, Su Muwan,
and Ling Shenxing
are no longer related.